Now that we have our zip file downloaded and unzipped,
既然我们已经下载并解压了 zip 文件
we need to open the extracted CSV file so that we can see and work with the data inside.
我们需要打开提取出 CSV 文件 以便我们能看到并使用内部数据
We'll do this by importing it into a table like structure in
方法是 使用叫做 Pandas 的 Python 库
our Jupyter Notebook using a python library called Pandas.
将文件导入一个表格结构 如同 Jupyter Notebook 中的一样
Pandas, created by West McKinney,
Pandas 由 West McKinney 创建
is an open source library providing high performance,
它是一个开源库
easy to use data structures and data analysis tools for the Python programming language.
为 Python 编程语言提供易于使用的数据结构和分析工具
Using Pandas is standard and best practice for data analysis in Python nowadays.
如今 使用 Pandas 是 Python 数据分析的标准和最佳做法
In the context of the gather step of wrangling,
在整理收集步骤的背景下
Pandas can import pretty much every file format you can think of,
Pandas 可以导入你能想到的任何文件格式
plus link to databases.
而且可链接到数据库
I'll cover the Pandas basics here,
这里我将讲述 Pandas 的基础知识
but if you'd like to know more,
如果你想知道更多
I recommend that you check out our Pandas course if you haven't already.
我推荐你了解一下我们的 Pandas 课程
There's a link to that in the notes below this video.
视频下方注释中有一个链接
So, Pandas will let us view and work with their CSV file in a simple,
所以 Pandas 以简单的表格格式
tabular format, known as the panda's data frame.
让我们查看并使用 CSV 文件 这种格式称为 Pandas DataFrame
Think of the data frame like a spreadsheet,
DataFrame 就像电子表格一样
but easier to manipulate using code and more powerful in general,
但使用代码更容易操控 功能整体上更强大
but not as good for browsing through data sets.
但浏览数据集却没那么方便
Okay, so our task,
好的 所以我们的任务是
import a CSV file into a panda's data frame.
将一个 CSV 文件导入 Pandas 的DataFrame
This is actually what I do every time to
这就是每次以找到操作方法所做的事情
figure out how to do this, Google is your friend.
Google 可以帮忙
So, I search "import CSV Pandas" and hey,
搜索 “导入 CSV pandas”
first result, the read_csv function.
第一个结果出来了 read_csv 函数
Read CSV, comma separated file into data frame.
将CSV (逗号分隔文件) 读入 DataFrame
Let's actually copy and paste the description
我们来复制和粘贴这个函数的描述文字
of the function to add a comment to our code.
并给我们的代码添加一个备注
Okay, so the main argument and accept is the path to
好的 主要结果是我们想将此 CSV 文件读入
the CSV file that we want to read into our Jupyter Notebook.
Jupyter Notebook 的CSV 文件的路径
You can ignore the rest for now.
你可以暂时忽略其余内容
If we scroll to the bottom,
如果我们滚动到页面底部
we'll see that the function returns a data frame.
我们将看到该函数返回一个 DataFrame
Okay, so let's go back to our Jupyter Notebook and first,
好的 我们回到 Jupyter Notebook
we'll actually have to import the Pandas library,
首先 我们必须导入 Pandas 库
which we customarily do, like so.
我们一向这么做
Import Pandas as PD which is called aliasing.
导入 Pandas 为pd pd为它的别名
In this case, so we don't have to type out four extra letter,
在此种情形下 我们不必打出四个额外的字母
shortening Pandas to PD as coders, so efficient.
将 Pandas 缩减为 pd 非常高效
And we process that cell, and we'll go back down here,
我们处理那个单元格 然后回到下面
and type in pd.read csv and we'll name the result of this function,
键入 pd.read_csv 并对此函数结果进行命名
the data fragment returns DF, short for data frame.
数据片段返回 df 即 DataFrame
This is a common convention.
这是一个常见的惯例
So, all that's left now is filling out the file path parameter,
所以 现在要做的工作是填写文件路径参数
which you can go check out here,
你可以在这里查看
or using a new feature that we haven't talked about yet called shift tab completion.
或使用一个尚未讨论过的新功能 即 “shift tab completion”
If you click shift tab here,
如果你点击 shift tab
you'll see the signature of the function
你将看到函数的署名
and the file path or buffer argument we need to fill in.
看到我们需要填入的文件路径或缓存参数
Okay, so fill that in now.
好的 现在就填入